I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Belle Ame...It means
"beautiful spirit" in French.
Bugger off. Hit the road.
-Jim, give me that!
-After all, Eddy is just a guy.
-Hey! They're waiting for us.
-Why are you saying this now? Shit!
-But, that makes Dying Breed appealing.
-What shall we do? That's irresponsible.
Hey Jim! What are you filming!?
-On top of that, Matt is wild.
Like a river flowing,
inspiration always flows from my mind.
-Hey! Dancing, dancing...Party man...
-Oh! He's a funny guy.
-Happy birthday to you...
Sometimes, there comes a special day,
while they're on tour.
It's a beautiful scene.
Tokyo...a city of noise
and chaos. Techno-city.
Come on!
They had a live here, as well.
In the evening, with the shining moon.
They met a boy. It was
a very special event.
"Fishing Hole"
A long time ago, a female office worker
quit her job for no good reason...
and started the
Grateful Sound Summer Special
with some music-lover friends.
It all started when she was blown away
by the Glastonbury Festival in England,
and wondered if fans couldn't put together
a pure rock festival here in Japan.
Grateful Sound started
from that simple motive.
Nowadays, it's the biggest
outdoor event in Japan.
Are you that office worker?
No...She was my sister,
who died last year.
I see...
Sorry for being so blunt,
but I have to talk business.
Sure...
You're friends with a member
of Dying Breed, aren't you?
Huh?
I heard that two of their members
were at your live performance.
Yeah...
Couldn't you get them, Dying Breed,
to come to the Grateful Sound event?
What?!
They just finished their
world tour and are off now.
"Live 20
'Grateful Sound'”
They just finished their
world tour and are off now.
"Live 20
'Grateful Sound'”
Yeah...I know that, but I'm asking...
"Live 20
'Grateful Sound'"
Hm...
Nowadays, Grateful Sound seems
like just a money-making tool.
I feel like it's moving
in the wrong direction.
Ran, the Japanese producer,
is planning to push one of the bands on
his label-a boring band called Belle Ame
featuring a young actor
named Yoshito Morozumi.
You know, my sister was someone...
who thought that music could change
the world consciousness of people.
Ran and Leon Sykes' RJ label can
only produce "feel-good" pop tunes.
"Escapist" music that
says everything is all right
just paralyzes people's consciousness
and steals away their ability
to solve the problems
that they face in their everyday lives.
Yeah...
Of course, it doesn't really matter
that there are so many "feel-good"
pop groups out there...
...but I don't want Grateful Sound
taken over by groups like those.
You say music has the power
to change the world?
Yes...At least Dying Breed does!
I like you, Aunty...
A-Aunty?!
I'll get in touch with Eddy right away.
You will?!
That is, if you let us
perform at Grateful Sound.
-Oh!
Actually...After hearing
Mongolian Chop Squad's CD,
I brought up your name, at one time...
To replace Loud Crime City,
who suddenly broke up.
Of course, your quality doesn't even
touch that of the other pro bands...
Hmm...Hmph!
Considering your future
possibilities and low cost,
there were some who agreed with me.
Mm...
-But...
-Huh?
Ran overruled me.
I don't know the reason,
but in this industry,
if you get on the wrong side of Ran,
it could be difficult getting ahead.
That's why I want to do it.
With backup from you and Leon,
it won't be impossible.
I think he said he'd stop by in two weeks,
on his way back from Australia...
I've decided! I'm going to
negotiate with Leon Sykes.
I hope you'll help us too, Aunty...
Aunty? My name is Kazuo Sato!
Wasn't it great?
Yeah. Eddy's so awesome!
What about Matt?
A little scary, I think.
And that boy who sang...Who is he?
I've never heard of Yukiko...
You too, Atsuko?
What? You're performing
at Grateful Sound?
Yeah, well...I'm getting together
with a new band called Belle Ame.
We plan to release an album this Fall.
-A singer?
-That's great!
-Umm...
-Let's see...
Let's get something to eat.
Oh...I pass.
Huh? What a wet blanket...
I'm kinda worried
about Ryusuke-kun's injuries.
Ah...I was just watching a movie...
So long!
What, from now?
Maho...Eguchi-san,
Yohei Takami and Chiemi Kuniyoshi
are at that place I told you about.
Oh? They have a terrific salad there. Oh...
I think Koyuki likes Chiemi Kuniyoshi...
I have all her CDs. I'm her biggest fan!
Oh, didn't you say you were
worried about Ryusuke's injuries?
He just needs to put some spit on them!
Um...Sorry, but no outsiders...
Oh...Then...
Tell Ryusuke I said "Hi."
Well, it'll all work out.
Listen, how can you be so sure?
I dunno.
Can't you give us a good explanation?!
When you're hungry,
you get snippy, don't you?!
You wanted to meet
Chiemi Kuniyoshi so much?
Yeah...I don't think
I'll be able to sleep tonight.
I...
I had a dream once...
There was a wide open space
that seemed to be veiled by mist,
and there was lots of trash...
Hot!! Damn you!
Are you trying to kill me?!
That trash...They were
picking it up, right?
The spirits of dead rockers...
-Huh?
"We're cleaning up after
your concert," they said.
Sid was doing it like he
didn't really want to, right?
A-After I saw that dream,
my fever had gone down and...
I don't know how they feel about it,
but there are bands that are
born from miraculous encounters.
Not anyone would do.
They're the only ones who could do it.
Hey, wait a minute!
I never saw a dream like that!
I-I always dream in panoramic,
full-color, 3-D.
I haven't seen any dream that foretells
our performance at Grateful Sound!
Uh, Chiba-kun, it's just a dream...
But! I'm the only one
who didn't have that dream...
Chiba-kun, your noodles are getting mushy.
Shut up, will you!
So was that dream
in black and white? Color?
Hm...I wonder...
Probably color.
What the heck...Aw, forget it!
Huh?
What is it? Someone fooling around?
Ouch!
Yo!
Oh...I'm so sorry!
You've gotta be quiet,
or you'll wake my mother.
Yeah...
You're okay now, Ryusuke-kun?
Yeah, well...
Why'd you two drop in like this?
Well...I wanted to see
your surprised face!
Here!
Huh? What is it?
"Kuniyoshi"
It's the real thing.
This...Could this be?
It's Chiemi Kuniyoshi's autograph.
Wow!
Hey...Your folks are gonna get up.
W-What's she like?
Mm...Well...A nice girl,
like she is on television.
Ah...
She said to tell you "Hi."
I'm going to treasure it.
Thanks a lot, Maho.
Hm?
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes..."
Boy, you've really grown up, haven't you?
Stupid brother...
Koyuki...Why was this magazine
by your pillow?
No reason...
Oh...I'm beat.
Koyuki, can I stay overnight?
Huh? But I've got only one bed.
Well, y'see...Ryusuke's bedding stinks
and it's full of lice.
Shut up.
Besides, Ryusuke's here too.
No. I'm going home. I can't
sleep in a strange bed.
Okay, well...Take care of her.
Ray!
Ouch...Listen, I'm injured, you know...
Take care...
See ya later.
Be careful...
Say, do you have something
I can change into?
Uh, just a minute...
I...I'm going to do some composing...
Okay. Well, good night.
Koyuki? Come over here,
if you're going to sleep.
Huh?
'Kay...
Koyuki...
-Koyuki...
-Huh?
You really looked great
in that movie, Koyuki.
Truly...You looked really great.
Thanks...
You know...
We kissed that day...
What did that mean?
Or, what do I mean to you?
Maho...Are you asleep?
"Thank you, Koyuki.
6:30 a.m. I'm going home. Maho"
You really looked great
in that movie, Koyuki.
Mm...Good morning...
Good morning.
-What?!
-Quit dawdling, will you?
Hurry up and wash your face and eat.
Y-Yeah...
Maho-chan...
Please help yourself to seconds.
Thank you.
My mother, that night, was really scary.
Listen to me! When a man is going
to act like a full-fledged man...
-he has to be able
to take full responsibility...
-Yes, ma'am...
Yes...
Hey, I don't see baldy
with golden teeth today.
You showed up in front of me again...
You must be crazy.
I brought the Beck's favorite today.
Hmph...
Beck is super shy
and gets so lonely easily.
Maybe because it came
from the way he looks.
So take good care of him.
I heard the Mongolian Chop Squad made it
to the top 10 in the U.S. College charts.
Uh-huh...
You could say that's quite
a big hit for that kind of music.
I guess the movie worked.
If they weren't from some
minor Indies label from Chicago
they woulda done a lot better, I think.
Maybe you're right.
What do you want?!
Are you here for the dog food, or what?
It's the Grateful Sound...
What the fuck?!
Now, take your time!
Concentrate! You can't be good
at anything unless you concentrate.
Yo! Tanaka-kun...
Oh, Kigata-kun...You're into wrestling?
Well, I have my eye on the Olympics.
That's impressive!
You and Hiromi-san get on well, don't you?
Oh...we do?
Hm...I think she probably...
likes you.
That's not...
Excuse me...
I saw the movie...
Can I have your autograph?
-Ee...Aah...
-Who, me?!
Koyuki-kun!
Hiromi-chan...
I saw it! The movie...
I went to see it yesterday, with a friend.
Really?
I was so impressed!
You were so big on screen.
The kids in the class
are all talking about you.
Oh?
I wanted to tell you that, so I came
running in my leotard-so embarrassing...
T-Thanks...
Bye!
I still have a lot to learn...
but I'll be happy if the movie
does some good for Beck...
Then...summer will come.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Next week, Page will
shoot beams from his eyes.
-Next week! Watch it!
-Write Music. Are you serious?!